<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<seiscomp>
	<plugin name="S-AIC">
		<extends>global</extends>
		<description>
		The S-AIC plugin computes S picks triggered by P picks by
		computing a running AIC. It works on the L2-norm of the
		horizontal components. S-AIC-V works on the vertical component.
		</description>
	</plugin>
	<binding name="S-AIC" module="global">
		<configuration>
			<group name="spicker">
				<group name="AIC">
					<description>
					AIC is an algorithm to pick S-phases based on an existing
					P-phase. In module configuration use the spicker interface name
					"S-AIC" for picking on the horizontal components or
					"S-AIC-V" for picking on the vertical comonent. Add the plugins
					&quot;saic&quot; for the detector and &quot;spickdbg&quot; for
					the graphical debugger to globel module configuration.
					</description>
					<parameter name="noiseBegin" type="double" default="-10" unit="s">
						<description>
						Start time of the signal processing relative to the triggering
						P pick. This adds a margin to the actual processing and is useful
						to initialize the filter (e.g. STALTA). The data is not used
						at all for detection until signalBegin is reached.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="signalBegin" type="double" default="1" unit="s">
						<description>
						Start time of the S-phase detector relative to the triggering
						P pick. Delaying the detector ignores P-coda and early signals,
						e.g. due to P-S phase conversions at shallow depths.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="signalEnd" type="double" default="60" unit="s">
						<description>
						End time of the S-phase detector relative to the triggering
						P pick.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="filter" type="string" default="&quot;RMHP(1)>>ITAPER(2)>>BW(3,3,8)&quot;">
						<description>
						Filter applied on the raw horizontal traces to compute
						the L2 trace. As a minimum remove offsets. S-AIC-V,
						filters the raw vertical trace computing the filtered
						vertical trace.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="detecFilter" type="string" default="">
						<description>
						Filter applied on the L2 trace before detection (S-AIC)
						or filtered vertical trace (S-AIC-V). For S-AIC-V either
						configure filter or detecFilter.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="step" type="double" default="1" unit="s">
						<description>
						The AIC time window stepping in seconds. For every step
						the window is expanded by step and the AIC is computed.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="minSNR" type="double" default="5">
						<description>
						Mininum SNR as returned from AIC for accepting a
						detection.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="minCnt" type="int" default="3">
						<description>
						Minimum number of hits for a particular pick time
						when the running AIC is computed for accepting a
						detection.
						</description>
					</parameter>
					<parameter name="uncertainty" type="string" unit="s">
						<description>
						Defines the pick time uncertainty. Either a symmetric
						uncertainty as single number or an asymmetric uncertainty
						in the following format: &quot;(0.5,0.25)&quot;. The first
						value: uncertainty befor the pick, second value: uncertainty
						after the pick.
						</description>
					</parameter>
				</group>
			</group>
		</configuration>
	</binding>
</seiscomp>

